[PENNY GIGGLING OUTSIDE]
PENNY:
Oh, my God, she didn't.
(Leonard:)What could she possibly be talking
about for so long?
(Sheldon:)Obviously, waitressing
at the Cheesecake Factory...
(Sheldon:)...is a complex socio-economic activity...
(Sheldon:)...that requires a great deal
of analysis and planning.
Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)You know, using positive
reinforcement techniques...
...I could train that behavior out of her
in a week.
(Sheldon:)-No.
-If you let me use negative reinforcement...
(Sheldon:)...I can get it done before we go to bed.
(Leonard:)You're not squirting her in the face
with water.
(Sheldon:)No, of course not.
(Sheldon:)We're talking very mild electric shocks.
(Sheldon:)No tissue damage whatsoever.
(Leonard:)-Forget it.
-Oh, come on.
(Sheldon:)You can't tell me
that you're not intrigued...
(Sheldon:)...about the possibility
of building a better girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)I'm not.
(Leonard:)Penny's qualities, both good and bad,
are what make her who she is.
[PENNY GIGGLING]